Oh, but...
That's Diryama's Essex's quest...
Fat Bomber...
Shouldn't we?
No questions.
We're so many nữa States of the lạions.
There's nothing to do!
Not that..
You should've been there
and I've been there
Let's go.
I don't know what's going on with Genya, but thanks to him I figured something out.
Even if we behead all four at the same time, we can't finish them off like we did Yutaro.
It's almost like attacking them at all is completely pointless.
Nezuko!
Something's been bothering me all this time.
Is it possible their neck isn't their vital spot?
Something's off.
That scent I caught for an instant.
Right.
That was...
The scent of another demon!
There's a fifth demon!
I've gotta find it.
The fifth demon's head's gotta be...
Listen, Brad.
I'm beating this upper rank.
By myself!
Genya!
Don't forget.
There's a reason you haven't become a Hashira.
You weren't able to defeat a upper rank six on your own!
Oh, uh... okay.
Then you can bet your life that...
I'm going...
To beat you to it!
Genya, what's going on with you?
You're drooling.
Not to mention you're choking me.
I'll be the one who becomes a Hashira!
That's great!
I believe in you.
You have Nezuko's in my full support.
Let's give it our all.
There's a fifth demon somewhere.
If you buy me some time, I can look for it.
You're just trying to get me to let my guard down!
Don't think I don't know what you're...
Huh?
Look out!
The anger demons revived already!
Hurry!
Genya!
I need you to keep these demons at bay!
While I look for the fifth!
Damn it!
They've all regenerated!
But whatever you do, don't slash Nezuko!
She's my little sister!
Where's that fifth demon?
I've got to find it while Genya and Nezuko are fending them off!
Hold on.
Thanks to the wind created by that fan demon,
the sulfur smell from the hot springs is gone!
Concentrate...
And find it!
It's all gonna be okay!
They'll never find me in this spot!
Surely my four emotions are strong enough to defeat those villains for me!
There!
Found it!
I found it!
Genya!
Urogi!
Start heading northeast!
The fifth demon's hiding itself close to the ground!
Genya!
You go after it! I'll stay!
North East!
Crap! Here comes the lightning!
Nezuko! Go and help Genya!
Stop the lightning demon before it gets in Genya's way!
Don't let go! You can't let yourself get swept away!
Oh no! Here comes that lightning attack!
Nezuko!
Is it excruciating? It must be excruciating!
So it's the same everywhere.
Not only are you unable to unleash your precious breathing techniques, but you'll soon be drawing your last breath in there too!
That makes stoic look on your face!
How incredibly sublime it is!
My creative juices are simply gushing looking upon it!
Don't fight back.
You're making me sad.
Sakido!
Hold the girl still, so I can crucify her!
That little brat!
He's gone even faster than before!
No.
From the moment I first met him, he's exceeded my lord's reports!
He has quick reflexes.
A keen battle sense.
And the closer he is to defeat, the stronger he gets!
Dammit.
Karaku!
That's far enough, you punk!
Alright!
Now to take care of that trigger-happy kid.
What?
He still slashed me?
You damn punk!
Genya!
To your right!
It's on your right, moving south!
Search for it!
What do you think I'm doing?
I've been searching for it!
A spell?
Can I not see it because of some type of spell?
Damn!
Where are you?
The longer this goes on, the closer I get to being depleted!
Turn west!
More to the right!
It's nearby!
Below!
Where is it?
Where?
Genya!
Below!
It's puny!
This is the main body?
So tiny!
Damn it!
How the hell am I supposed to shoot something that moves around like that?
This demon is no bigger than a field mouse!
But those other four are crazy strong!
This whole time he's been controlling them?
We have to fight off four demons at once while chasing this mouse!
What a pain!
Now I can see why so many demon slayers keep ending up dead!
Don't mess with me, you annoying ruts!
You're really starting to piss me off!
I can do this!
I can win!
I can't slash it!
No way!
Look at it!
His head is no bigger than my finger!
That didn't work!
Oh crap!
I was too slow!
I can't get out of the way!
I'm gonna die!
I won't be able to regenerate my neck!
Big brother...
I wanted to become a Hashira
So that my big brother would acknowledge me
And so I could apologize to him
For what I said that day
I can still remember
Just how small Mother was back then
Even when I was younger
I was somehow already taller than she was
From morning till night
Mother was always keeping herself busy working
Come to think of it
Not once did I ever see her take a break
Or even sleep
On the other hand
My father was a big guy
And a good for nothing
He got stabbed to death
By someone with a grudge against him
Serves him right
After all
The old man was always beating up
On his own wife and kids
Using that tiny body of hers
Mother would put herself between us and our father
All in order to try and shield us from his beatings
She was an amazing person
Hey, Mom's late
Isn't she?
Genya
You're still awake
Yeah, but so are you
All right
I'm going to look for Mom
Wait
I'll go too
No
I want you to stay home
I can do this by myself
Huh?
We promised, remember?
Yeah, of course
Right
I'll be back
Brother
What gives?
Why are all you guys awake too?
You promised you think Mom's okay?
She's fine, all right?
Big bro just went to look for her to make sure
Yeah, but...
It's so late
She's never been out this long at night, has she?
The sun's already about to come up
It's gonna be okay
I bet you're tired
Go back to bed
You'll see
Mom and Big Brother will be back by morning
That must be her!
Mom!
Wait, don't open it!
It might not be Mom that's at the...
Is it a beast?
A stray dog?
No, it's a wolf
It's too dark to see
It's fast!
Kenya, run away!
Brother!
No!
Koto!
Shuyo!
Hiroshi!
Teiko!
Sylvie!
Put pressure on your wounds!
I'll go get the doctor!
Just hang on a little longer!
I don't know what's going on
What was that thing back there?
And where's Brother?
No
I have to get the doctor first
Brother...
Mother!
Why'd you do it?
What made you want to kill our own mother?
Murder!
You murdered her!
I'm sorry I said those awful things, Brother
Forgive me
It's all...
It's all just excuses, but...
I was in a panic
Shuya, Hiroshi, Koto, Teiko, and Sumi were all lying there dead
Not answering me
It's over
In that very moment, I knew I would die next
And that rabid wolf
Or at least what I thought was a wolf
Was our mother who turned into a demon
You risked your life fighting her to protect us
And carried her outside towards Daybreak
That moment
When you first realized that it was Mom who was attacking our family
I can't imagine how that made you feel, Brother
Standing there, lifeless and shattered
After killing our beloved mother
And having your brother that you fought to protect denounce you
I can't imagine how that made you feel
When we just promised each other
That we'd do everything we could to protect our family
Genya
It's up to us now to protect the family
Dad got himself killed, after all
And while things will be easier without him around
Without a father
Everyone might start to feel hopeless
From now on
It's up to you and me
To do our best to protect our whole family
Got that?
But we always have, haven't we?
Now's no different
Right, bro?
I'm sorry, brother
I'm going to die without getting a chance to apologize
Even with my life flashing before my eyes
That memory of you smiling is at the front of my mind
I'm not like you, brother
I don't have any talents of my own
I can't use breathing techniques
And I'll never become a Hashira
And if I never become one
I'll never meet other Hashira
I gave it my all
But it wasn't enough
A scumbag like yourself
Could never be a brother of mine
You're better off quitting the core
You don't mean that
I may have changed
But I'm still your younger brother
Kenya
You can't give up
Try again
Try slashing it again
You gotta keep trying
You can't give up
I'll protect you
Concentrate solely on beheading it
Aren't you gonna become a Hashira?
Kenya Shinazugawa
Oh no
Behind us
Weeping spears
This is bad
She hit me
Dead on
Go
Kenya
I can't
Beheaded
It has to be you
Who does it?
So just this one time
I'm going
Kenya
To let you have it
I'll do it
No matter what
There it is
It's tiny
You're not getting away
conferencing
плюс
You're not getting away
com
don't look at the
HP
Thank you.
I said I don't want anything!
Roy's acting too buddy-buddy.
Because we're friends.
What makes you think we're friends?
We soaked in the hot springs together.
Look, that was only because you barred Zimta!
And our final selection class.
That makes us friends, right?
Uh...
Look here.
I told you to stop being so-
Hold that thought!
Next, episode 7.
Awful villain.
Genya, let's always be friends.
We're not friends!